## **Stephen Scaff**

# **Design Technology Leader**

#### Contacts

site — stephenscaff.com
email — smscaff@gmail.com
tel — 206.371.8547
github — github.com/stephenscaff
linkedin — linkedin.com/in/stephenscaff
dribbble — dribbble.com/stephenscaff

#### Bio

I work at the intersection of design + code with a focus on interaction and the front-end experience. I've built and led design-minded development teams at creative agencies and big tech companies, actively contributing to some of the most used products on Earth (Alexa, eBay, Redfin, etc). Born in Pittsburgh PA, I now live in Seattle WA, with my wife and 3 kiddos.

#### **Education**

BA Writing - University of Pittsburgh 2008

## **Experience**

#### Sr. Design Technology Manager

2020 - current

**eBay** — Started Design Technology as a practice for eBay Design, building and managing a team of amazing design-minded engineers (DTs). My team helps to bridge the design/development gap, inspiring investment in new ideas and solving tough design challenges through code & technology. Oversee creation of production-minded prototypes and tools to improve design processes. Active across multiple areas of the business (Buyer, Seller, etc), along a variety of initiatives, in an assortment of technologies (web, native, Figma plugins, etc).

#### Design Technologist / UX

2019 - 2020

Amazon/Alexa — Worked on Design Technology initiatives at Amazon's Device Design Group (DDG), supporting Alexa's various forms. Focus was on the Alexa Design System and Alexa Platform Language.

## **Development Lead**

2017 - 2019

**GreenRubino**— I led the Agency's web development offerings, managing a team of developers and designers and modernizing the firm's stacks and processes. Notable clients; Kidder, Columbia Bank, Milliman, NHL, BloodWorks.

## **Head of Front-End Development**

2014 - 2017

**Urban Influence** — Headed interactive / front-end development for the Seattle-based firm, helping the agency win a multitude of Site of Day/Developer Awards (Awwwards, FWA, CSSDA), including runner up for Awwwards Small Agency of the Year. Notable clients: Quentin Tarantino, Formidable, Beechers, INRIX, Redfin, Watson, Chefn, SeattleMet, Capital Pacific, Ink+Volt